Yeah
Sweet dreams come after hours
甘い夢は後からやってくる
달콤한 꿈은 느지막이 찾아와
Los sueños dulces llegan tarde
甜美的梦姗姗来迟
Nothin’ that’s not allowed
禁じられたものは何一つない
금지된 건 아무것도 없어
No hay nada prohibido
没有什么不被允许
You should never sleep alone (sleep alone)
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない (sleep alone)
혼자 잠드는 일은 절대 없을 거야 (sleep alone)
Nunca deberías dormir sola (sleep alone)
你永远不必孤单入眠 (sleep alone)
Cuz I’ll always take you home (yeah right)
どんな時も僕が君を家まで送るから (yeah right)
내가 항상 널 집에 데려갈 테니까 (yeah right)
Porque siempre te llevaré a casa (yeah right)
因为我永远都会带你回家 (yeah right)
When there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl
身にまとっている時
걸쳤을 때
Que un collar de diamantes
那一刻
I just wanna love ya like love ya like love ya like that
僕はただそうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
난 그저 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Solo quiero amarte así, amarte así, amarte así love ya like that
我只想那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
Love ya like love ya like love ya like that
そうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Amarte así, amarte así, amarte así
那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
(Then) you love me right love me right love me right back
(そして) 君は僕を同じように そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
(그럼) 네가 날 똑같이 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
(Entonces) tú también ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
(那么) 请你也像我一样那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
Love me right love me right love me right back
そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
Ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
You should never sleep alone
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない
혼자 잠드는 일은 절대 없을 거야
Nunca deberías dormir sola
你永远不必孤单入眠
Cuz I’ll always take you home
どんな時も僕が君を家まで送るから
내가 항상 널 집에 데려갈 테니까
Porque siempre te llevaré a casa
因为我永远都会带你回家
When there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl, oh
身にまとっている時
걸쳤을 때, oh
Que un collar de diamantes, oh
那一刻
Any night, any time, you are my appetite
どんな夜 どんな時も 君は僕の好みそのもの
매일 밤, 언제나, 넌 내 취향 저격이야
Todas las noches, a cualquier hora, eres mi apetito
每个夜晚，每分每秒，你都击中我的心房
Double vision Gemini and it goes like this
二つに見える まるで双子座みたいに まさにこうやって始まるんだ
둘로 보여, 마치 쌍둥이자리처럼, 바로 이렇게 시작되지
Doble visión, como Géminis, así es como comienza
双重幻影，恍若双子座，故事就此开始
Take you home, take it slow
君を家まで送る ゆっくりと始める
널 집에 바래다줘, 천천히 시작해
Te llevo a casa, lo tomamos con calma
带你回家，慢慢开始
‘Til you bite your lip
君が唇を噛むまで
네가 입술을 깨물 때까지
Hasta que te muerdas el labio
直到你轻咬嘴唇
Got a movie in my mind and it goes like this
僕の頭の中には1本の映画が浮かぶ まさにこうやって始まるんだ
머릿속에 영화 한 편이 그려져, 바로 이렇게 시작되지
Imagino una película en mi mente, así es como comienza
我脑海中勾勒出电影画面，故事就此开始
Closed curtains, open eyes
カーテンは閉まっていて 目は開いている
커튼은 닫혀 있고, 눈은 떠 있어
Las cortinas bien cerradas, los ojos abiertos
窗帘紧闭，双眼睁开
Lay down your skin on mine
君の肌を僕の肌に重ねる
네 살을 내 살과 맞대
Pon tu piel sobre la mía
你我肌肤相贴
Leave all the rest to me
その先は全て僕に任せて
나머지는 다 나한테 맡겨
Y el resto déjamelo a mí
剩下的都交给我
Yeah
Sweet dreams come after hours (that’s what they do)
甘い夢は後からやってくる (that’s what they do)
달콤한 꿈은 느지막이 찾아와 (that's what they do)
Los sueños dulces llegan tarde (that’s what they do)
甜美的梦姗姗来迟 (that’s what they do)
Nothin' that’s not allowed (uh huh)
禁じられたものは何一つない (uh huh)
금지된 건 아무것도 없어 (uh huh)
No hay nada prohibido (uh huh)
没有什么不被允许 (uh huh)
You should never sleep alone (sleep alone)
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない (sleep alone)
혼자 잠드는 일은 절대 없을 거야 (sleep alone)
Nunca deberías dormir sola (sleep alone)
你永远不必孤单入眠 (sleep alone)
Cuz I’ll always take you home (yeah right)
どんな時も僕が君を家まで送るから (yeah right)
내가 항상 널 집에 데려갈 테니까 (yeah right)
Porque siempre te llevaré a casa (yeah right)
因为我永远都会带你回家 (yeah right)
When there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl
身にまとっている時
걸쳤을 때
Que un collar de diamantes
那一刻
I just wanna love ya like love ya like love ya like that
僕はただそうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
난 그저 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Solo quiero amarte así, amarte así, amarte así
我只想那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
Love ya like love ya like love ya like that
そうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Amarte así, amarte así, amarte así
那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
(Then) you love me right love me right love me right back
(そして) 君は僕を同じように そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
(그럼) 네가 날 똑같이 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
(Entonces) tú también ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
(那么) 请你也像我一样那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
Love me right love me right love me right back
そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
Ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
You should never sleep alone
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない
혼자 잠드는 일은 절대 없을 거야
Nunca deberías dormir sola
你永远不必孤单入眠
Cuz I’ll always take you home
どんな時も僕が君を家まで送るから
내가 항상 널 집에 데려갈 테니까
Porque siempre te llevaré a casa
因为我永远都会带你回家
When there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl, oh
身にまとっている時, oh
걸쳤을 때, oh
Que un collar de diamantes, oh
那一刻
You the only cover that I need when I’m cold
寒い時に必要な唯一のカバー まるで毛布みたいに
내가 추울 때 날 감싸줄 수 있는 유일한 너
Eres lo único que necesito para cubrirme cuando tengo frío, como una manta
你是我寒冷时唯一需要的庇护，像毯子一样
You can have my body with my heart and my soul
僕の心と魂 身体まで全てを捧げられる
내 맘과 영혼, 내 몸까지 다 줄 수 있어
Puedo darte todo, mi cuerpo, mi corazón y mi alma
我可以给你我的心和灵魂 甚至我的整个存在
You light up my life, you’re like a diamond
ダイヤのように僕の人生を照らしてくれる君
다이아몬드처럼 내 삶을 밝혀주는 너
Eres como un diamante que ilumina mi vida
你如钻石般照亮我的生命
Shinin’ shinin’ shinin’, yeah
輝く 輝く 輝く yeah
빛나, 빛나, 빛나, yeah
Brillas, brillas, brillas, yeah
闪耀 闪耀 闪耀 yeah
And we might never get to sleep tonight
今夜は眠れないかもしれない
오늘 밤은 잠을 못 잘지도 몰라
Puede que esta noche no durmamos
今夜或许无法入眠
I’ll give you everything you need tonight
今夜は君が求めるものを全てあげる
오늘 밤엔 네가 필요한 것 모두 줄게
Esta noche te daré todo lo que necesites
今夜我会给你想要的一切
This kind of love I guarantee for life
このような愛を一生約束するよ
이런 사랑 나는 평생 약속해
Te prometo este tipo de amor para siempre
这份爱 我用一生承诺
Dreams gonna be sweet tonight
今夜 僕らは甘い夢を見るんだ
오늘 밤 우린 달콤한 꿈을 꿀 거야
Esta noche tendremos dulces sueños
今夜我们将共赴甜美梦境
Sweet dreams come after hours
甘い夢は後からやってくる
달콤한 꿈은 느지막이 찾아와
Los sueños dulces llegan tarde
甜美的梦姗姗来迟
Nothin’ that’s not allowed
禁じられたものは何一つない
금지된 건 아무것도 없어
No hay nada prohibido
没有什么不被允许
You should never sleep alone (sleep alone)
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない (sleep alone)
혼자 잠드는 일은 절대 없을 거야 (sleep alone)
Nunca deberías dormir sola (sleep alone)
你永远不必孤单入眠 (sleep alone)
You should let me take you home (alright)
君を家まで送らせて (alright)
내가 널 집에 데려가게 해줘 (alright)
Déjame llevarte a casa (alright)
因为我永远都会带你回家 (alright)
‘Til there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl
身にまとっている時
Que un collar de diamantes
那一刻
걸쳤을 때
I just wanna love ya like love ya like love ya like that
僕はただそうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
Solo quiero amarte así, amarte así, amarte así
我只想那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
난 그저 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Love ya like love ya like love ya like that
そうやって君を そうやって君を そうやって君を愛したい
그렇게 널 그렇게 널 그렇게 널 사랑하고 싶어
Amarte así, amarte así, amarte así
那样爱你 那样爱你 那样爱你
(Then) you love me right love me right love me right back
(そして) 君は僕を同じように そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
(그럼) 네가 날 똑같이 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
(Entonces) tú también ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
(那么) 请你也像我一样那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
Love me right love me right love me right back
そうやって僕を そうやって僕を そうやって僕を愛して
그렇게 날 그렇게 날 그렇게 날 사랑해 줘
Ámame así, ámame así, ámame así
那样爱我 那样爱我 那样爱我
You should never sleep alone
君が一人で眠りにつくことは 絶対あってはいけない
넌 혼자 잠드는 일이 절대로 없어야 해
Nunca deberías dormir sola
你永远不必孤单入眠
Cuz I’ll always take you home
どんな時も僕が君を家まで送るから
내가 항상 널 집에 데려갈 테니깐
Porque siempre te llevaré a casa
因为我永远都会带你回家
When there’s nothin’ left but diamond necklace
君がダイヤのネックレスだけを
네가 다이아몬드 목걸이만 걸쳤을 때
Cuando no lleves nada más
当你只戴着钻石项链
On you girl
身にまとっている時
걸쳤을 때
Que un collar de diamantes
那一刻